[{"answer": "Well, I can tell you that both Obama and the Romney campaigns think that.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Are we all just watching the final vestiges of this race when actually Romney has already crossed the line?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "That's a great point.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "But say he lost in Pennsylvania, doesn't his dignity then say he must pull out then?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Well, it is entertaining, and if you read the book, you'll see it's for the camps very tense and scary.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "So Evan, what was your conclusion so far about this race in terms of its merit as a political challenge?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well, if Mike Allen reports it, of course it's true.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "I think that, but listen, there's a fight within the Romney campaign because some people do want him to come out and show a more human side.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Don't you think?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "No, that's right.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "I mean he's a pretty good guy when it comes to basic normal human values, isn't he?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, look, I mean, two weeks ago I was here with you and you were talking about our big wins and then we went on to win Louisiana and we've won already 11 states.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "How do you come back from this?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Well, let's put it this way.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "If Mitt Romney kicks Rick Santorum's butt in Pennsylvania, in his own backyard, isn't that game over?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, Barack Obama himself called out Newt by name today.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "How many times did he come last in these primary battles now and retain credibility as a candidate?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "That's what all the pundit say, but Newt Gingrich has been counted out before and we're going to have a three-week lull now with -- I think for some it's a law, for others it's an opportunity to have a conversation to make sure that we continue to unify at least a message, at least in principle, if not in process at the moment.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "The question becomes who backs who and surely all the polls tell you and all the momentum tells you that Newt would have to throw support behind Rick Santorum, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "You know what, it's a power of delegates, it's the power of wins, it's to cut the burn rail a little bit on the spending.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "What is the roadmap ahead for the Romney campaign?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, it's not my call.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "At what point do you think other candidates should pull out of this race?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I think that's more of a function of the Santorum campaign quite frankly, and the Democrats are using some of Senator Santorum's verbiage to their electoral advantage, to their partisan advantage.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "How does he rebuild trust in the female vote?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I think a little bit.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Is he champing it a bit to get in?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "The media tends to play you the Etch A Sketch stuff.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "And what do you think, as one of his friends, he needs to do to stop making those kind of mistakes?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, I've always seen this as almost like a prize fight, Piers.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Are you feeling like the wedding is on its way here?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Yes, the horse has bolted.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Is this feasible or has the horse bolted?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Well, I think he needs to do a better job at fighting back against the media.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "How is he going to turn around the perception of himself in tough economic times that he's simply out of touch with the average American?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Well, I think those are all great things, but I think there's a difference between being nasty and campaigning dirty which I think you could argue that he kind of does, but also being an aggressive campaigner.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "You know, is he just too nice a guy?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Well, I think, Piers, we've seen that President Obama is having a little bit of a mini meltdown.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Which camp are you -- and I know you like Romney, but if you're President Obama, are you feeling vulnerable or confident tonight?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Well, the White House is hoping in terms of unemployment that the trend is going in the right direction for them.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not a -- I'm not a gambling man, but I do think --", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Where is your money going?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "The conventional wisdom surely right now is that Romney is a pretty weak nominee, that -- but these things that we saw go back and forth.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "So he's a skilled man, he's a good businessman, he's intelligent, but he's got a real uphill battle, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Cantor.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Who should be Mitt Romney's running mate?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "Very likely to be Rubio.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Ben?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Rubio.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Carol?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Well, he -- you know, he didn't do the Hillary --", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Why is it so crazy?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "What about Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "120403pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "ORGAN: She's better this time than last time, right?", "qSentId": 609}]